<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation Engineering</title>
    <link>https://smiskiewicz.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Automation Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 21:56:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://smiskiewicz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://smiskiewicz.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 21:56:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smiskiewicz.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a dude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in software for almost a decade working on Continious Integration, Software Deployment, Operations, Testing and automating all kinds of things.  I&amp;rsquo;ve currently been focused on a microservices architecture and all the joys that come with it, good and bad.  Posts will probably be about the tools and tech I deal with every day.  So expect some fun Jenkins, Docker, and Ansible posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is my attempt at the legal stuff.  All of my code is free to use, if you want to post about it yourself please note this site as a source.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://smiskiewicz.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 22:27:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smiskiewicz.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a blog! I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start documenting some things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from my experience in building and deploying web applications at scale.  The internet has provided me free job training on a regular basis and I felt this was a way I could help give back to the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus will be on the things I do from a day to day basis: continous integration, software deployment, configuration management and operations.  If you want to learn more about me feel free to checkout the about section.  I have yet to setup a comments section, if you have any please send them my way via a direct message on twitter @stevemiskiewicz&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>